Here we go, Upcomi!
This time we have with us Rin Kawana of Angerme and Rocco Tsutsui of Ocha no Ma!
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you our recording, rehearsal and other production processes.
Music
So, first of all, let's take a look behind the scenes at the two mc's. I, Kawana, am wearing an earmony during the live performance on the tour.
Kawana has been wearing ear monitors since the middle of the tour because the audience's voices are too loud for her ears.
It's a little harder to hear the audience than without ear monitors, but with such a change, the information from my ears is lost and my eyes become clearer.
I was able to see the audience's expressions and discover new things, and I was able to hear the songs differently and feel them differently.
It was a new experience for me.
I don't know...
I don't often have a chance to wear ear monitors, so when I wear them, I can hear the way I sing.
I don't get a chance to wear ear monitors very often, so when I put them on, the way I sing or the way I hear is totally different, so I'm a bit confused and find it very difficult to sing like I usually do.
I'm currently on a live house tour that will take me to all 47 prefectures of Japan.
The other day I went to Shimonoseki in Yamaguchi Prefecture and visited a place called Kanmon Strait.
There is a bridge connecting Fukuoka and Yamaguchi prefectures, and when I went there for the first time, I could see the straits on the other side of the bridge.
When I went there for the first time, I didn't think it was Fukuoka Prefecture, but when I asked the girl who went with me, she said it was Fukuoka Prefecture.
I was like, "Wow, Fukuoka Prefecture looks so close from Yamaguchi Prefecture, which is so close to Yamaguchi Prefecture.
It was a great discovery.
And then we went to Osaka, and when we were in line at the takoyaki restaurant, the old man in front of us bought takoyaki for us.
How kind!
I felt so warmth!
Wow, that's so nice!
Yes, both teams are working hard on their tours, but we don't often have time for sightseeing, so I hope we can do it someday.
Okay, then.
First of all, here's the making of the music video shoot for Hanawa Miyamoto's "Bambina Bambina Bambie.
Here's a look at the making of the music video for "Bambina Bambina" from Hanawa Miyamoto's latest single, which was released on November 8!
Yes, ma'am.
Making of...
Yes, today we are shooting the music video for "Bambina Bambina," and I'm here with my make-up and all that,
This song is one of the most passionate songs that Hanashi Miyamoto has ever written, and it's the kind of song that makes you feel like you're about to get excited,
I'm looking forward to seeing how everyone will react when they hear it for the first time.
The set is also very gorgeous, so I will do my best for the whole day.
Yes, we are going to do our best for the day.
Yes, we will decide on this side of the stage,
Yes, with your hands on.
Yes, put them on. See you later.
Yamaguchi Miaka Yun
ака
imi
upwards
To do what is natural to me.
I just want to be more frightened by it all.
I care about
me
You can try to sing a fun theme.
Then it's over
Just your coaches.
We want to lift you up.
Festival
We'll take you as far as you'll go
We'll take the heat for you
One, two, three
I'm trying too hard
I'm on tenterhooks
You've got to take it all in stride
I want to be stopped, and then I start to move my face a little bit, like I'm trying too hard
It's a sparkle with words
It's the Meat Bambi of congratulations
I've been working too hard. I'm exhausted.
Give me a good time, please.
A great love sour
Give me a chance to fend you off
Now it's your turn Bambi
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
It's like it's your turn now
It's Meat Bambi.
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
If you hold the camera like this, it's kind of soulful, so...
Yes, and then decide to be a little bit cooler or cooler.
Yes, and take off the lines and stuff.
Yes, good, good, good, good, good
Yes, good, good, good, good, good.
A little bit like a real feature at the end.
Yes, catto!
ED
Thank you for watching!
That's good, that's good, that's good, that's good.
Now please roll the camera.
See you later.
Thank you.
Yes, it's almost like this.
You want me to lean out more.
Can you lean out this far?
There's this, and I'm riding out like I was just now.
Yes, I will go now.
Thank you for watching.
I'll do my best.
Okay, go ahead and get into it.
ana
veeno
Doing what is natural
That's all there is to it.
I can't stop.
No!
We're all pushing ourselves.
We're all just too old to know better.
We're tired and we want to hurt you so bad.
We get away!
We're always doing it afterwards.
It's not the voices that get us here.
We're digging up the map of where you fell.
I want to make it up to you
I want to fly with sparkling cherry blossoms
I'll wake up score stealer
I'm trying too hard. If I can get two out...
We both wish
You're perfect for you
Yes, we finished shooting the music video. I was so excited to see the sparkling costumes that they made for us this time,
I especially want you to pay attention to the dance, which is a little different from the previous ones, because it is so bumbie bumbie,
I would like you all to imitate and dance along with me, and the fact that Bambie is a girl and Bambie is a boy makes it easier to imitate,
I hope that everyone will watch and imitate the song. The song itself is a very uplifting song, but if you read the lyrics carefully, they are very deep,
The theme of this single, in particular, is self-affirmation,
I would be happy if you feel your self-esteem has been raised after listening to this song,
I'd be happy if you feel your self-esteem has been raised after listening to this song. This is Hanashi Miyamoto. Bye bye.
I thought this song is packed with various elements, and the music video also shows that, with various scenes developing, I thought it was very ingenious.
I am not very good at making facial expressions, but Ms. Miyamoto's facial expressions were very well suited to the lyrics and the theme of self-affirmation came across very well.
This is the making of the shooting of the music video for Hanashi Miyamoto's Bambi na Bambi.
Thank you for watching.
I've been working too hard and I'm a bit of a goofball.
I've been working too hard, so I'm a little grumpy.
You're having fun?
Having fun? Please watch the rest of the show.
And now, here we go.
Theater Girls Club, starring the Beyons.
Biospy's Missing Attache Case Big Book Reading
At the National Teaching Materials Co-op Hall Space Zero
Starting on November 10th.
Theater Girls' Club Starring Beyonds
of "Biospy's Missing Attache Case
Please watch the meeting and reading of the play!
Thank you for watching!
Squeezing it out is super crack! I have a good happy feeling and I work in the wedding industry,
And by the way, if you stop by, there's a lot of residuals and no time off, and that's why it's a crack!
I'm Rika Shimakura and I play Mika.
This is the first time for me to play a bright uniform like Mika's, so I'm very energetic and cheerful on set,
I hope I can always do my best as Mika.
I will do my best to make this a work that will be loved by everyone by putting on all the energy of BEYOND.
Thank you very much for your support.
How can I be assigned to kill one spicy killer for every 1,000 young people on a daily basis?
I have no choice but to succeed without mistakes.
Let me tell you the quantity. My name is Makoto Maeda.
I am very excited to hear that there will be action this time, as I have always wanted to try my hand at it.
I will do my best as a quantity.
I look forward to working with you.
When I walked into this café, I thought there were similar attache cases.
It's trendy, it's not good, and I didn't have it on hand.
I will play YUKI. I am Shiori Misuta.
I'm also new to action, so I'm so frail that I really can't even train my muscles,
I have a compact period of one month, so I hope I can play the role properly and be able to be a spy.
I will do my best. I look forward to working with you.
You mean you will deliver it to one of our people who is undercover in the East? Who is it?
It is just before the hour.
Just deliver it to that person. That's all you need to do?
Yes, sir.
This is Takase-kun of Isa Ayako.
When I read the script, at the end, I thought, "Oh, is this for real?
I think she is a child who lives in the work all the way through, so I wondered how I could express that,
I hope I can do something that will not be obvious at first sight, but will make people who have seen it many times think, "Oh, my God!
I will do my best. Thank you very much.
With our fellow West Japanese, failure is never an option.
I am Mitsumiyo, English translator.
This is the first time for me to see an action, but I am interested in dance as a point of interest,
I hope to make the most of the aliveness and simplicity, and I also hope to make the most of such things,
I hope to make the most of such things, and since Mr. Hiiragi is here, I personally hope to learn a lot about him,
I hope to learn a lot from Mr. Otani. I will do my best. I look forward to working with you.
The mango parfait I wanted to eat, the mango parfait of my choice.
The mango parfait of the 1950s, let's eat it in a big hurry.
A sparkling jewel, I will take it.
Yes.
Hello. My name is Chiyokana Sato.
It's my first time to play a role with this kind of atmosphere, so I'm the older sister in the Japanese chart,
I hope that many people will love Mako-chan,
I will do my best with energy.
It is also my first time to act, so I will do my best to make it look cool.
I look forward to working with you.
Please take care of me too. But I'll eat.
I have to be an accomplice to Makoto, too.
I'm sorry. Two mango parfaits.
Okay.
I'm Saya Imi and I play Haruka.
It's been a while since I've played a girl, so I'm really excited.
I'm also really looking forward to the action. I look forward to working with you.
A man who charms the world with his magic.
Actually, this is a secret story between us.
The charm of the character.
From the richest man in the world, I'm here, properly.
I'm Yune Yamazaki, playing the role of Mr. Sho.
This is my first time playing a male role, but I've always wanted to do it, so I'm really excited.
I'll be up for the magic too, so please give me your best.
I look forward to working with you.
Mr. Urahiko presents.
Mr. Sho's magic show, The Disappearance, will be set up tonight at 7 p.m. as planned, but we will be broadcasting a live benefit interview that will last about an hour.
Yes, I'm Rena Ishimoto.
I'm Rena Ishimoto, the theater actress.
Well, I play the role of Beeman Manager by myself, so it seems like we can support Mr. Sho together. I look forward to working with you.
I've been doing a lot of work and being silly.
Anyway, can we meet today?
Today?
Yeah, today.
I'll be working in the management section.
This is Mohime today.
I'm a straight shooter, and since I don't think anyone else is here, I'm going to cry really hard myself, and I'm going to love this rehearsal and do my best to perform. I will love this rehearsal and try my best to play the role.
An ordinary, boring day suddenly takes a turn.
It is thanks to the gems.
Shine on the stars.
This is with silver.
Yes, a gift from God.
I will be playing Nanami. My name is Minami Okamura.
When I read the script, I was a little nervous because it's a tough role, but Nanami is a very happy girl.
I'm a little nervous, but Nanami is a very happy-go-lucky girl, and I think she's very cute in a happy-go-lucky way, so I'm going to do my best to bring out that lovely atmosphere. Thank you very much.
My heavenly brother. Look at you at a glance.
Aren't they just like two people together?
I will be playing the roles of Light and Lightning.
My name is Manaka Kobayashi.
Well, this is my first time playing a male role, and it's also my first time playing two roles, so I'm very nervous, but actually this is my first time playing the piano as Hikaru, so I will do my best by acting. I will do my best.
Yes, thank you very much. This is the stage for the beauty spy missing attache case.
Yes, I am. This is the stage for "The Beauty Spy's Missing Attache Case".
Yes. The stage begins.
It was a rejection reading.
After the reading, I realized that this play is a slapstick spy drama, or rather, it is a pop and fun play with a message in it,
So, it is very important for each character to have his or her own beliefs in order to convey the message of the play to the audience.
I realized that it is very important to convey the message of the play to the audience.
This time, the general setting is a parallel world in Japan.
There is a country of Japan that is divided into the west and the east, and the spies who belong to each side struggle to survive.
The spies who belong to each of these two countries struggle against each other.
And there's a magician's role.
I'm wondering what will happen when the various characters get involved.
And as the subtitle says...
The missing attache case.
It's like a slapstick show over an attache case.
So it's going to be a slapstick story about a missing attache case, so it's going to be fun and funny.
But this time, it's a spy story, so there will be action scenes.
I'm sure there will be some action scenes.
It will be a stage where you can enjoy both the charm of the new Bjorns and the charm of the old Bjorns.
I think it's going to be a play where you can enjoy both.
I play the role of Lisa.
Rika Shimakura's character Mika belongs to.
Assignment? She belongs to a different organization.
She's like a member of an organization.
She's going to be your classmate.
We'll be like classmates.
Lisa... is a character I'm still trying to figure out.
I'm still trying to decide on her character.
I'm still trying to figure out what's inside of her.
She's a girl who has a grip on things.
I'm not sure how I'm going to express that.
I'm happy to think about how to express that while having fun.
I would be happy if I could think about how to express that while enjoying the performance.
And also
Mika, the character I play, is a really bright girl.
She's a really cheerful girl.
She makes everyone around her happy.
Happy, but
But she's also a key person who gets involved in a lot of things
She's also a key person.
I think she warms up the scene for everyone.
I'm not really like that, but usually
I'm not really like that, but I feel like if I played Mika, I could be like that.
I feel like I could be like that if I played this Mika.
I think she has a lot of power.
I'm going to do my best to finish the play with energy and cheerfulness.
I'm going to do my best to finish the play in a cheerful and bright way.
There will be a Tokyo performance and an Osaka performance this time.
I'm sure it will be a longer performance than usual.
I'll take care of myself and have fun.
I hope you all enjoy the show and take care of yourselves.
Please come and see us!
Here's a look at the reading of the script for the play starring the Beyons!
The play is set in Japan, a futuristic city divided into East and West.
It is a story that takes place in Japan, a future city divided into East and West.
The content is very good, so please check it out!
I'm very anxious to see it.
I've never performed on stage before.
I've never been on stage before, but I did it in school.
I made some mistakes with my lines.
I made some mistakes.
I felt it was very difficult.
I would like to try acting and performing on stage, but
But I'm sure you must be very nervous and anxious.
I think it's really cool.
Do you have an interest in acting, Mr. Kono?
Yes, I do.
I've performed in one of Yoshikazu Miyamoto's plays before, but I was so nervous that I couldn't do it well at all.
I was so nervous that I couldn't do it well at all.
At that time, I was so nervous that I couldn't do well at all.
I've also seen your past performances.
I remember I was really moved by the way he got into the role as if he was a different person.
I remember I was really moved by the way she got into the role as if she were a different person.
That's why I'm really looking forward to seeing you in this play.
Beyonds's leading role in the play
Theater Girls Club
Beyonds Pie: The Missing Attache Case will be performed
at the National Mutual Insurance Co-op Hall Space Zero
at the National Mutual Insurance Co-op Hall Space Zero on November 10.
Why don't you come and see it!
Theater Girls Club
This is a scene from the reading of the script for "Byospy's Missing Attache Case".
I'm sure you'll be fine as usual!
This is Apkami with Rin Kawana of Angerme and Tsutsuki Roko of Ocha-no-Oma!
Next up is here!
Morning Musume。23 Bake Up Call When You Wake Up
Vocal recording by Sakura Oda
From Morning Musume。23's latest single
Please take a look at the vocal recording of Sakura Oda from the latest single of Morning Musume。
I'm going to start with the first melody, so I'm going to try to make it a little stronger, a little more flavorful, a little more peculiar, so that it doesn't match your make-up.
I'm going for a slightly badass, blunt look.
That kind of makeup doesn't suit you.
It's an imposition of femininity that can't be erased.
I'm going with love, not for you
That's all I'm trying to say
It's not for you.
Can you go a little harder?
I'm not doing it for you.
Not for you.
Okay, yes.
Okay, a little harder there.
Yes, ma'am.
You don't look good in that makeup. It's an imposition of femininity that can't be removed.
Unfortunately, it's not for you. That's all I'm saying.
Okay.
Okay, let's do the second half of the melody.
Unfortunately, it's not for you. That's all I'm trying to say.
I'm just saying, it's not for you.
A creature with a destiny. Every face must be affirmed.
Any face.
You've got to get up there.
This is really hard.
Accent the head with four lines.
Cute, cool, mocking, and fake.
A creature with a destiny. Every face has to be positive.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry, I'm not doing this for you. That's all I'm saying.
Cute, cool, mawkish, fake, fake, fake, fake.
A creature with an instinctive need to affirm every face.
And you know what?
Cute, cool, mawkish, and sincere.
I was thinking, like, a different nuance for each line.
Give me a four-line head like that.
Okay.
Unfortunately, it's not for you. That's all I'm trying to say.
Cute, cool, mocking, and sincere.
Okay, I'll go next.
A creature with a conscience. I have to affirm every face.
I'll give it to you alone.
It's so boring to leave it to others.
I'll decide for myself... and I'll never waver in my decision.
I don't want to deceive myself
I am... Pronunciation?
Pronunciation.
I'll make it a little fuller, a little more resonant.
Alone La La La lilala lilala lilala lilala lalalalalalalala
I think it's okay for her to have a core color like that.
It's getting a little too cute right now.
Yes, ma'am.
Me.
I'm sure it's boring to leave it up to others... but I'll decide for myself... and I can't shake this feeling... that I want to be a bar owner.
I've got a game, so let's play a little rusty.
I want to do the store bar I want to wake up and enjoy life
The sun is this girl
Goo...
tee
goo tee
I'll light up the dance
Dabi dance dabi dance dabi dance dabi dance dabi
That's right, that's what it's like.
Kami ikakko, kami ikakko, kami ikakko
It could be "kakko kakko" or something like that
But it's a little too cool. It sounds a little too cute.
Let's try something a little cooler.
It's time to enjoy life. That's what the sun says.
Just do it Just do it Just do it Just do it
By H.
I'll do the dance for you, I'll do the dance for you
Spree dance spree dance spree dance spree dance spree
Yeah I think this is about as vigorous as it gets
Shall we dance at the bottom of the night
Yes, sir.
The sun is in my heart and it's a long way to go
Spree dance spree dance spree dance spree
In the depths of the night, morning and night, I'll tell you my heart
I'll throw it away
Yeah, perfect.
Now it's time to go down
Someone's heart waiting for morning
Okay, let's rap.
Be cool!
Yes, sir.
I light up the brightness
Davi da da da da da da da da da da da da
You can't see yourself only in the bread
You have to experience life to realize it
People have to be a little kinder
If you give up, you'll never find the real peace
Oh, it worked, didn't it?
Yes, it worked.
Yeah, it worked.
Okay, so we got all the shots.
Yes, sir.
Okay, we're done.
Thank you very much.
This song has a very wide range, from the bottom to the top, and there are various rhythms in it.
I thought it was a very difficult song from the first time I heard it, so I was very moved to see you singing it so well.
I was also impressed by the way you sang the song, not only the rhythm and such, but also the way you expressed yourself in such detail.
As soon as she was told, Sakura Oda changed the way she sang, which I often think is very difficult to do, so I was very impressed to see her do it immediately.
I thought it was really cool that she did it right away, and I thought it was really cool that she said "the peace" when she rapped about it.
And when he says "The Peace" in his rap, he changes his costume for a moment in the music video.
When I saw it for the first time, it was amazing and gave me goosebumps.
It really takes you back in time, doesn't it?
I thought it was great that it was there for a moment.
This is Morning Musume。23 Wake Up Call Wake Up When You Wake up Vocal Recording of Sakura Oda
That one lie is the end of everything, Buze.
Morning Musume。23 すごいフィーバー 南無音サーヨ
Thanks for watching.
Rin Kawana and Suiroko here at Apkami.
It's time to say goodbye!
We've seen a lot of different videos this time, but I, Tsutsui, would like to thank Sakura Oda for all of them.
I, Tsutsui, saw Sakura Oda's vocal recording.
The rhythm of this song is very difficult.
I thought it was really cool how well she handled the rhythm of the song.
I, Kawana, saw the shooting of Ms. Yoshikazu Miyamoto's music video.
Although only one person appeared in the music video, it was very satisfying to watch.
I thought it was amazing that they were able to make a video with such a high level of satisfaction.
In APKAMI, we will go behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UPFRONT Group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we'll introduce you to the parts you don't normally see.
This time on Apkami, we have Rin Kawana of Angerme and Ocha no Oma Naotsukiroko!
Good bye.
Next time on Afkhami
Morning Musume。23
Zukoi Fever
The making of music video shooting
and
Tsubaki Factory
Recording of "Yuuki It's my life" will be released!
Please look forward to it!
Thank you for watching!